Carol Nacher

Quality Analyst

Montevideo, Uruguay

(+589) 98 632 008

carolnacher@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/carol-nacher-81b25820a/

https://github.com/carolnacher

About Me

I am a Functional QA. I have experience in performing exploratory, black box, and smoke testing for both applications and the web. I have experience in tools such as Postman and MySQL. I am currently improving my programming skills. With 7 years of experience in another field, I excelled in team environments, met tight deadlines, and understood detailed requirements. I am confident that my skills and commitment to learning can contribute significantly to a company.

Work Experience

RoHa.Deva / Qa freelance.

Febrary 2023 - Present, Montevideo, Uruguay

My tasks included software testing, black box, Android-specific testing, and efficiently reporting bugs through Trello. My experience includes creating and executing test cases in TestLink, focusing on improving user experience (UX). Verify the integration of the payment gateway, particularly with MercadoPago, and guarantee compliance with the requirements of the user plan. Proficient in test case generation and mobile testing.

Architectural Draftsman /Partial

August 2010 - Feb 2023, Montevideo, Uruguay

My task focuses on improving client experiences, alleviating construction-related stress, and delivering hyper-realistic, technical visualizations to help make the project process smoother while minimizing errors and future dissatisfaction.

Baby Up / Saleswoman

March 2010 - Dec 2010, Montevideo, Uruguay.

My tasks consisted of serving the public, showing and selling the products according to the client's needs, replenishing and controlling the stock of each product, and maintaining the premises, also for a short time, I worked as a cashier.

Education

BYU-Idaho /Web and Computer Programer

April 2023 - Present. Online

This career is aimed at learning different programming and design languages such as JavaScript, Python, and HTML among others. Providing experience in teamwork, leadership, and delivery times.

Software Testing / QA junior

Jun 2022 - Oct 2022, Montevideo, Uruguay

An intensive course covering SQL, MySQL Workbench, Postman, API testing, and development tools. I mastered database management through SQL and MySQL Workbench, honed my API testing skills with Postman, and became proficient in using development tools for comprehensive software analysis. The course provided a practical understanding of the key tools essential for effective software testing and quality assurance.

ORT /Interior Design - Technical

April 2009 - April 2011

Career aimed at learning various styles and techniques of interior design, in the use of programs such as Autocad, Archicad, and Sketchup for the planning, execution, and visualization of each project. Providing experience in team and individual work.

High School/Bachelor

complete November 2006, Montevideo, Uruguay

Recognitions

I completed in April 2022 EnglishConnect 3, aimed at learning and improving language skills. In April 2023, completed the BYU-Pathway Worldwide course improving my communication skills in English at the level of writing and oral expression.

Provides me opportunities

- -Leadership, by allowing us to lead a class.
- -Time management in the delivery of jobs and projects.
- -Knowledge in Mathematics.

Reference

Lucia Pereyra / Senior Manager

Phone: +598 99 860 486

Tatianna Nieves/ QA Engineer and Testing Trainer

Phone: +598 91 037 314